[
  {
    "unique_id": 1,
    "question": "Almost every Korean meal involves kimchi What is this?",
    "optionOne": "fermented spicy cabbage",
    "optionTwo": "rice",
    "optionThree": "seasoned bean sprouts",
    "optionFour": "soup",
    "correctAns": 1,
    "category": "Food"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 2,
    "question": " Which noodle dish is primarily eaten in the summer?",
    "optionOne": "kalguksu",
    "optionTwo": "japchae",
    "optionThree": "mul naengmyeon",
    "optionFour": "ramyeon",
    "correctAns": 3,
    "category": "Food"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 3,
    "question": "What is the main ingredient in the Indian sweet 'Gulab Jamun'?",
    "optionOne": "Rice Flour",
    "optionTwo": "Wheat Flour",
    "optionThree": "Gram Flour",
    "optionFour": "Milk Solids",
    "correctAns": 4,
    "category": "Food"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 4,
    "question": "Which Indian dish is made from marinated paneer cooked in a spiced gravy?",
    "optionOne": "Butter Chicken",
    "optionTwo": "Chicken Tikka Masala",
    "optionThree": "Palak Paneer",
    "optionFour": "Shahi Paneer",
    "correctAns": 4,
    "category": "Food"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 5,
    "question": "Which spice is commonly used in Indian cuisine and is known as the 'Queen of Spices'?",
    "optionOne": "Cumin",
    "optionTwo": "Turmeric",
    "optionThree": "Cardamom",
    "optionFour": "Saffron",
    "correctAns": 4,
    "category": "Food"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 6,
    "question": "Which monument is called Blessing Scenery Palace",
    "optionOne": "Gyeongbokgung Palace",
    "optionTwo": "Statue of King Sejong",
    "optionThree": "Sungnyemun Gate (Namdaemun)",
    "optionFour": "Cheong Wa Dae",
    "correctAns": 1,
    "category": "Monuments"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 7,
    "question": "Which Indian monument is located in Agra and is a UNESCO World Heritage Site?",
    "optionOne": "Hawa Mahal",
    "optionTwo": "Charminar",
    "optionThree": "Qutub Minar",
    "optionFour": "Taj Mahal",
    "correctAns": 4,
    "category": "Monuments"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 8,
    "question": "Which monument is the largest and most famous structure in Delhi, India?",
    "optionOne": "India Gate",
    "optionTwo": "Red Fort",
    "optionThree": "Humayun's Tomb",
    "optionFour": "Lotus Temple",
    "correctAns": 2,
    "category": "Monuments"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 9,
    "question": "Which Indian monument is a medieval sandstone fortification located in Rajasthan?",
    "optionOne": "Amer Fort",
    "optionTwo": "Golconda Fort",
    "optionThree": "Jaisalmer Fort",
    "optionFour": "Red Fort",
    "correctAns": 3,
    "category": "Monuments"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 10,
    "question": "Which Indian monument is a group of structures built as a tribute to a beloved queen?",
    "optionOne": "Hawa Mahal",
    "optionTwo": "Victoria Memorial",
    "optionThree": "Lotus Temple",
    "optionFour": "Charminar",
    "correctAns": 2,
    "category": "Monuments"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 11,
    "question": "Which flower is considered the national flower of India?",
    "optionOne": "Lotus",
    "optionTwo": "Rose",
    "optionThree": "Sunflower",
    "optionFour": "Jasmine",
    "correctAns": 1,
    "category": "Flowers"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 12,
    "question": "Which flower is known as the 'Queen of Flowers' in India?",
    "optionOne": "Marigold",
    "optionTwo": "Hibiscus",
    "optionThree": "Lotus",
    "optionFour": "Rose",
    "correctAns": 4,
    "category": "Flowers"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 13,
    "question": "Which flower is used extensively in Indian religious ceremonies and weddings?",
    "optionOne": "Lotus",
    "optionTwo": "Jasmine",
    "optionThree": "Rose",
    "optionFour": "Tulsi",
    "correctAns": 2,
    "category": "Flowers"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 14,
    "question": "Which flower is often associated with festivals like Diwali and Holi in India?",
    "optionOne": "Marigold",
    "optionTwo": "Dahlia",
    "optionThree": "Chrysanthemum",
    "optionFour": "Lily",
    "correctAns": 1,
    "category": "Flowers"
  },
  {
    "unique_id": 15,
    "question": "Which flower is used to make garlands and is commonly seen in Indian weddings?",
    "optionOne": "Sunflower",
    "optionTwo": "Orchid",
    "optionThree": "Jasmine",
    "optionFour": "Rose",
    "correctAns": 3,
    "category": "Flowers"
  }
]
